## RESUME

### Erik Jon Dunwell

# 2528 WINTERBROOK DRIVE | LAWRENCE KANSAS 66047 ERIK.CEO@ICLOUD.COM | TEXT/CELL, 785 764 8883

#### **TALENTS**

Dedicated as a true, honest, high performing professional...

Proactive and results oriented Senior Executive Assistant experienced in smooth and impreccable execution of any project, focusing on clear organization and first-rate arrangement of internal/external communication. Expert in legal and technical writing. Full attention to detail, cautious with style and confidentiality matters. Abel to flawlessly handle the whole range of management functions constantly keeping track of execution process. Top rated team player who is always calm dispute the pressure and kinstantly creates a productive atmosphere.

- Excellent communication, organizational and interpersonal skills; positive attitude.
- Full Apple computer hardware and software skills. Moderate Windows knowledge.
- Competency in legal and technical writing; exceptional grammar and spelling skills.
- Ability to multi-task and maintain productivity under extreme pressure.
- Strong teamwork skills while being efficient working alone/together.
- Perfectly compliant with all corporate procedures and laws.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Designing People | Lawrence KS USA | CEO/Founder Lawrence Kansas USA

January 2004 - present

CEO/Founder of my 501(c)(3) nonprofit. In person crisis intervention on both the local and midwestern state/regional level consisting of southern Nebraska, northern Oklahoma, western and Missouri/Kansas City metro area. Online intervention nationwide in the USA, due to expand into Europe/UK in late 2020. My primary clientele are those that are homeless, battered and critically mentally ill persons. As of this date I still remain a volunteer Founder/CEO and work directly with clients on a 24/7 daily basis.

AT&T Communications | Office of the Kansas CEO | Kansas Chief Executive Assistant to the Kansas AT&T CEO Kansas City Kansas USA

June 1982 - March 2017

Executive Assistant to primarily the main Kansas CEO with support also given to the CFO, and group of 4 executive level corporate attorneys. 30+ years of rock solid and dedicated work experience. I performed exemplary legal writing, organization and consistently formatted and maintained document databases on a 24/7 basis if need be. I was considered to be "on call" every other weekend to be expected to work remotely if need be. I maintained regular communication via telephone, text, email, fax, with other departments and professional departments all over the entire world as an international communications company. I arranged/managed all executives and attorneys schedules of all types. As the Senior Executive Assistant the last 10 years, at all times I was held responsible for the full spectrum of executive level tasks of any kind, all with very stringent time deadlines and performed at 100% accuracy, no matter what the situation at hand might have been. Finally, I provided full administrative support to lower level Executive Assistant positions at all times. I also organized and maintained a group of 15 entry level managers that were new college graduates seeking executive level function experience. My yearly base salary for 2016/17 was \$175,000.00 not including any premium performance bonuses/vacation. In January 2017 I accepted a formal severance and "buy out" package and March 2017 was my last working month with AT&T.

Saks Fifth Avenue Southern Texas Area Manager/Buyer | Women's Shoes & Handbags Houston Texas USA

January 1979 - December 1982

- High end women's accessory sales/buying. Primarily women's shoes, handbags & furs.
- My southern Texas territory was the top performing women's speciality area for my 3 years of employment.

**EDUCATION** 

LDUCATION

Duke University | School of Law Online Durham, NC USA

AA in Legal Studies; core emphasis, corporate law January 1995, A+ GPA, Magna Cum Laude graduate.

Southeast Missouri State University | School of Business/School of Broadcast Communications | Cape Girardeau, MO USA

Double Bachelors Degree | Public Relations & Business Administration | Minor, Abnormal Psychology A+ GPA, Magna Cum Laude graduate; Dean's honor roll; 5 years.

University High School | Private School, K-12 Cape Girardeau, MO USA General Diploma, Emphasis Communications May 1979, 4.0 student, all classes, all 4 years of high school.

PROFESSIONAL ASSOCIATION

American Bar Association 1991/no expiration

Please let me know how I can make this professional position and transition be of mutual benefit...

Best,

Erik Jon Dunwell

# References:

Mr. Benjamin Resch, Architect Lawrence Kansas USA benresch@outlook.com

Mrs. Lisa Lawrence, Attorney at Law AT&T Overland Park Kansas USA lisa.lawrencekansas@gmail.com

Dr. Ross Perez, MD Kansas City Missouri USA perez\_ross@att.net